{"0": {"question": "Anglia", "answer": "\u0410\u043d\u0433\u043b\u0456\u044f", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "1": {"question": "Francja", "answer": "\u0424\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0446\u0456\u044f", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "2": {"question": "Grecja", "answer": "\u0413\u0440\u0435\u0446\u0456\u044f", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "3": {"question": "Hiszpania", "answer": "\u0406\u0441\u043f\u0430\u043d\u0456\u044f", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "4": {"question": "Irlandia", "answer": "\u0406\u0440\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0434\u0456\u044f", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "5": {"question": "Litwa", "answer": "\u041b\u0438\u0442\u0432\u0430", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "6": {"question": "Niemc", "answer": "\u041d\u0456\u043c\u0435\u0447\u0447\u0438\u043d\u0430", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "7": {"question": "Norwegia", "answer": "\u041d\u043e\u0440\u0432\u0435\u0433\u0456\u044f", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "8": {"question": "Polska", "answer": "\u041f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0449\u0430", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "9": {"question": "Portugalia", "answer": "\u041f\u043e\u0440\u0442\u0443\u0433\u0430\u043b\u0456\u044f", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "10": {"question": "S\u0142owacja", "answer": "\u0421\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0447\u0447\u0438\u043d\u0430", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "11": {"question": "Szkocja", "answer": "\u0428\u043e\u0442\u043b\u0430\u043d\u0434\u0456\u044f", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "12": {"question": "Szwajcaria", "answer": "\u0428\u0432\u0435\u0439\u0446\u0430\u0440\u0456\u044f", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "13": {"question": "Szwecja", "answer": "\u0428\u0432\u0435\u0446\u0456\u044f", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "14": {"question": "Turcja", "answer": "\u0422\u0443\u0440\u0435\u0447\u0447\u0438\u043d\u0430", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "15": {"question": "Ukraina", "answer": "\u0423\u043a\u0440\u0430\u0457\u043d\u0430", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}, "16": {"question": "W\u0142ochy", "answer": "\u0406\u0442\u0430\u043b\u0456\u044f", "category": {"name": "Nazwy kraj\u00f3w"}, "hard": 50}}